<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--Credits -->
    <string name="me">Guillermo Alvarez Colman</string>
    <string name="ripple_guy">Robin Chutaux - Ripple Effect</string>
    <string name="blur_guy">Romain Guy - Blur Effect</string>
    <string name="engine_libgdx"> Libgdx </string>
    <string name="engine_android"> Android </string>
    <string name="cryptography"> Tozny LLC - Cryptography</string>

    <!--Licenses-->
    <string name="ripple_licence_heading">License for Ripple Effect</string>
    <string name="ripple_license_text">

        The MIT License (MIT)
        Copyright © 2014 Robin Chutaux
        Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
        of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
        in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
        to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
        copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
        furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

        The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
        all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
        AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
        LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
        OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
        THE SOFTWARE.

    </string>

    <string name="blur_license_heading">License for Blur Algorithm</string>
    <string name="blur_license_text">

      Copyright © 2007, Romain Guy All rights reserved.

	  Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
	  modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
	  met:

      * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
	  this list of conditions and the following disclaimer. * Redistributions
	  in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of
	  conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other
	  materials provided with the distribution. * Neither the name of the
	  TimingFramework project nor the names of its contributors may be used to
	  endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific
	  prior written permission.

	  THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
	  "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
	  TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A
	  PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER
	  OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
	  EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
	  PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR
	  PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF
	  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
	  NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
	  SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    </string>

    <string name="google_code_license_heading">License for Code by Google</string>

    <string name="google_code_license_text">

        Copyright © 2012 Google Inc.

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.
    </string>
    
    <string name="en_library_heading">License for cryptographic Library</string>

    <string name="en_library_text">

  Copyright © 2014-2015 Tozny LLC

  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
  THE SOFTWARE.

  Created by Isaac Potoczny-Jones on 11/12/14.
    </string>
    
    
    

</resources>